Techical Business Analyst ~ 3 months of experience

DUONG NGUYEN

1. 0946 292 494

duongnguyen.22@icloud.com <u>1</u> 22/02/1999

O District 10, Ho Chi Minh City.

(a) darleigh.com | LinkedIn

O MBTI: INFJ

Brief introduce

I genuinely want to use technology in my life to increase efficiency and provide long-term benefit for society. I believe that I have the qualities necessary to succeed. These qualities are demonstrated by my academic and extracurricular experiences.

Education

Bachelors, Ton Duc Thang University.

(2017-Expect 2023)

Software Engineering, GPA 7.03/10.

Class director: Good Rating.

Spiritual unity among 87 classmates to

grow together in knowledge and

common activities.

Certifications

IIBA Business Analyst Foundations Communicate

Google Project Management

Google UX Designer

Google Analytics

Google IT Python

IIG TOEIC R&L 530

Google Digital Marketing 9LX 7AB 5MF

Skills

Critical Thinking

Problem Analysis

Decision-making

Negotiation

Programming

Agile Plannning

Experience

BlockchainWork (10/2022-11/2022)

Digital Solution R&D • Webframe • Agile

In charge of current web3 product research and development, which includes:

- Analyze superiors' requirements and provide solutions to challenges.
- Create function for website to manage stakeholder and enhance user experience UIX.
- Describe the system's SRS document.

Luong Thanh Phat Company (05/2022 - 08/2022)

Techinical Collaborator • Django • Waterfall

Web applications provide digital transformation and processization of contract administration, enhanced tram information, and car rental partners using software.

HongHanh Wedding Services (05/2022 - Present)

Technical Co-Founder • Product Designer • Sales • Leadership • Waterfall

Applying digital transformation involves the use of cloud technologies in task management and work assignment to other jobs. Furthermore, self-employment allows me to better grasp the duties and processes involved in optimizing the efficiency of overtime labor.

Jobnet Vietnam (10/2020-02/2021)

UIX Designer Intern · Visual Designer · Webapp

In this employment, I was taught in fundamental programming abilities and website expertise, storing data about websites such as LandingPage, eCommerce.